Scenic Hudson Collection: Records Relating to the Storm King Case, 1963-1981
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 4. Federal Power Commission, 1964-1978; 4; About 4 linear feet Boxes: 28 - 40 Folders: 291 - 551
  - Order Dismissing Application for Rehearing and Vacating Order Permitting Intervention, Apr. 9, 1965 (Folder 298, Box 28)
  - Order Denying Application for Rehearing (Hilltop Co-op), Feb 19, 1965 (Folder 299, Box 28)
  - Petition of S.L.Udall, Sec. Of Interior, for Intervention, April 22, 1965 (Folder 300, Box 28)
  - Order Permitting Intervention -Cortlandt Citizens, April 26, 1965 (Folder 301, Box 28)
  - Petition of Intervention by the Natl. Party Boat Owners Alliance, Inc., April 26, 1965 (Folder 302, Box 28)
  - Petitions of Intervention by Taconic State Park Commission(Hudson Valley Project), April 28, 1965 (Folder 303, Box 28)
  - Grant of Intervention and Denial of Motion for Prehearing Conference and Continuance of Date of Hearing, April 30, 1965 (Folder 304, Box 28)
  - Order Permitting intervention of Sportsmen’s Council Marine Dist. Of NYS, April 30, 1965 (Folder 305, Box 28)
  - Opinion and Order Denying Application for Rehearing, May 6, 1965 (Folder 306, Box 28)
  - Order Permitting Intervention, May 14, 1965 (Folder 307, Box 28)
  - Commission Staff Brief, June 11, 1965 (Folder 308, Box 28)
  - Commission Staff Reply Brief, June 18, 1965 (Folder 309, Box 28)
  - Commission Staff Reply Brief, June 30, 1965 (Folder 310, Box 28)
  - Order Denying Application for Rehearing and Petition to Reopen Proceedings, July 1, 1965 (Folder 311, Box 28)
  - Opinion and Order on Issues regarding location of lines, Fish Facilities and Amending Licenses, October 4, 1965 (Folder 312, Box 28)
  - Scenic Hudson, et al vs. FPC and Con Ed, October 8, 1965 (Folder 313, Box 28)
  - Order Granting Additional Time for filing Petitions to Intervene, February 24, 1966 (Folder 314, Box 28)
  - Ruling on Request for Extensions of Time (Folder 315, Box 28)
  - Order granting continuance and Denying Motion for add. Prehearing Conference and Stay of Proceeding, June 3, 1966 (Folder 316, Box 28)
  - Answer to SHPC addressing Inquires to the Commission, July 1, 1966 (Folder 317, Box 28)
  - Answer of Commission Staff to Motion for a date certain for the filing of all Testimony and Exhibits by Opposing Interventions, July 11, 1966 (Folder 318, Box 28)
  - Presiding Examiner’s Ruling Denying Several Motions for Adjustments of Dates and the Setting of a Date Certain, July 25, 1966 (Folder 319, Box 28)
  - Presiding Examiner’s Ruling Directing a Conference with Respect to Inquires and Objectives, July 26, 1966 (Folder 320, Box 28)
  - Order Granting Intervention (to Fuels Research Council), August 9, 1966 (Folder 321, Box 28)
  - Order Denying Motion to Postpone Hearing and Order Denying Motion for Stay of Proceeding (Folder 322, Box 28)
  - Inventory of Recreational Facilities at Licensed HydroelectricProjects, December 12, 1966 (Folder 323, Box 28)
  - Commission Staff Brief, August 14, 1967 (Folder 324, Box 28)
  - Staff Reply Brief, September 5, 1967 (Folder 325, Box 29)
  - Commission Staff Supplemental Brief, November 6, 1967 (Folder 326, Box 29)
  - Examiner’s Initial Decision on Application for License, August 6, 1968 (Folder 327, Box 29)
  - Commission Staff Brief on Exceptions, September 7, 1968 (Folder 328, Box 29)
  - Answer of Staff to Petition of NYC for Leave to Intervene, November 4, 1968 (Folder 329, Box 29)
  - Amending Annual Report, February 3, 1969 (Folder 330, Box 29)
  - Ruling of Motion to Permit Late Filing of Rebuttal Testimony, February 19, 1969 (Folder 331, Box 29)
  - Stipulation, March, 1969 (Folder 332, Box 29)
  - Commission Staff Reply Brief, May 23, 1969 (Folder 333, Box 29)
  - Order re: Motion for Information on Proceedings of the Advisory Council on Historic Preservation, September 19, 1969 (Folder 334, Box 29)
  - Decision on Con Ed’s Application for License, December 23,, 1969 (Folder 335, Box 29)
  - Statements by John N. Nassikas, Jan. -Aug 1970 (Folder 336, Box 29)
  - License, August 19, 1970 (Folder 337, Box 29)
  - Application of Intervenors for Rehearing, September 17, 1970 (Folder 338, Box 29)
  - Application of NYC for Rehearing of Opinion and Order Issuing License, September 18, 1970 (Folder 339, Box 29)
  - Recommendations for Legislation to Spiro T. Agne, September 30, 1970 (Folder 340, Box 29)
  - Order Extending Time to Commence Project Construction, July 25, 1972 (Folder 341, Box 29)
  - Scenic Hudson Petition to Reopen Hearings, March 28, 1973 (Folder 342, Box 29)
  - No. 2338 CE Motion for Time Ext. to Ans. SHPC Petition, April 6, 1973 (Folder 343, Box 29)
  - No. 2338 CE Affidavit Supp FPC Ans. and Motion vs. SHPC (Folder 344, Box 30)
  - No. 2338 CE -CE Ans. To SHPC Pet. To Re -Open Hearings and Motion to Dismiss Pet. 5/14/73, May 14, 1973 (Folder 345, Box 30)
  - No. 2338 CE Affidavit, May 21, 1973 (Folder 346, Box 30)
  - No. 2338 CE Application/HRFA for Rehearing of Pet. and for PSP Reg. Order 7/2/73, July 2, 1973 (Folder 347, Box 30)
  - No. 2338 CE HRFA Suppl. Pet. For Hearing and PSP Reg Order 12/19/73, December 19, 1973 (Folder 348, Box 30)
  - No. 2338 CE Ans. Of CE to Suppl. Pet. Of SHPC/HRFA 1/18/74, January 18, 1974 (Folder 349, Box 30)
  - 2338 1/28/74 Reply of HRFA to Answer of Con Ed, January 28, 1974 (Folder 350, Box 30)
  - Petition of NYS Attorney General for Rehearing, April 4, 1974 (Folder 351, Box 30)
  - 2338 HRFA Answer to Pet. Regulating Pumped Storage Pro., April 10, 1974 (Folder 352, Box 30)
  - Project 2338 Con Edison City’s Pet. To Review/Stay 4/24, April, 1974 (Folder 353, Box 30)
  - Proj. 2238 Con Edison 5/14/74 Con Ed Answer to City, May 14, 1974 (Folder 354, Box 30)
  - Petition of SHPC: Proj. # 2338 Urging Stay of Con Ed 5/20/74, May 20, 1974 (Folder 355, Box 30)
  - Project 2338 CE Com. Staff Response to City Pet 5/24/74, May 24, 1974 (Folder 356, Box 30)
  - No. 2338 CE Reply of NYC to Answer of CE and SHPC Pet. (Folder 357, Box 30)
  - Proj. 2338 -CE 5/28/74 SH Response to City Pet For Stay (Folder 358, Box 30)
  - No. 2338 CE, CE Answer to Suppl. Pet. Of SHPC 6/3/74, June 3, 1974 (Folder 359, Box 30)
  - No. 2338 CE: Reply of NYC to Answer of Comm Staff 6/5/74, June 5, 1974 (Folder 360, Box 30)
  - No. 2338 CE Notice of Time Extension 6/10/74, June 10, 1974 (Folder 361, Box 30)
  - No. 2338 6/10/74 Response, HRFA, to SHPC Pet., June 10, 1974 (Folder 362, Box 30)
  - Answer of Palisades Interstate Park Comm. To NYC Petition, June 14, 1974 (Folder 363, Box 30)
  - No. 2338 CE: H. Samuels Pet. Reopen Hearings and Stay 6/17/74, June 17, 1974 (Folder 364, Box 30)
  - Proj. 2338 -CE Supp. To Pet. Of NYC Pres. Before Comm. 6/27/74, June 27, 1974 (Folder 365, Box 30)
  - 2338 7/3/74 petition of Howard Samuels to Intervene, July 3, 1974 (Folder 366, Box 30)
  - No. 2338 July 3, 1974 H. Samuels Pet. To Intervene (Folder 367, Box 30)
  - No. 2338 July 12, 1974 CE Rsp. To Pet. RE: Alternative (Folder 368, Box 30)
  - 2338 July 15, 1974 Ans. To SHPC Pet. -Stay Construction (Folder 369, Box 30)
  - No. 2338 July 19, 1974 HRFA Letter RE Fish Hearings (Folder 370, Box 30)
  - No. 2338 July 25, 1974 AC Ans. To Samuels Petition (Folder 371, Box 30)
  - 7/30/74 Order Fixing Hearing on Remand, July 30, 1974 (Folder 372, Box 30)
  - 2338 Notice of Pre-hearing Conference 7/31/74, July 31, 1974 (Folder 373, Box 30)
  - 2338 7/31/74 Staff motion for Pre-hearing Conference, July 31, 1974 (Folder 374, Box 30)
  - 2338 Aug 26, 1974 Lefkowitz Pet. To Intervene (Folder 375, Box 30)
  - 2338 8/30/74 NYS Att. Gen. Motion for Additional Testimony, Aug 30, 1974 (Folder 376, Box 30)
  - 2338 Sept. 3, 1974 SHPC Mo. To Vac. Dat. For Hear. (Folder 377, Box 31)
  - 2338 Sept. 9, 1974 Com. Staff Counsel Rsp to Mo. Vac. Hear Sch. (Folder 378, Box 31)
  - 2338 9/3/74 Motion of SH to vacate dates, Sept. 3, 1974 (Folder 379, Box 31)
  - 2338 9/9/74 Com. Staff Counsels’ Reply to Motion to, Sept. 9, 1974 (Folder 380, Box 31)
  - 2338 9/10/74 Lefk. Rsp Re: Mo. Vacate Dates, Sept. 10, 1974 (Folder 381, Box 31)
  - 2338 9/11/74 CE Reply vs. SH Motion to Vacate Schedule, Sept. 11, 1974 (Folder 382, Box 31)
  - 2338 9/12/74 NYS att. Gen.’s Reply, Motion to Vacate, Sept. 12, 1974 (Folder 383, Box 31)
  - 2338 9/13/74 Ruling on Motion of SH to Vacate Schedule, Sept. 13, 1974 (Folder 384, Box 31)
  - 2338 9/13/74 Com. Ruling on SH Motion on Scheduling, Sept. 13, 1974 (Folder 385, Box 31)
  - 2338 9/13/74 Order Granting Interventions, Sept. 13, 1974 (Folder 386, Box 31)
  - 2338 9/17/74 CE Motion for Time Extension, Sept. 17, 1974 (Folder 387, Box 31)
  - 2338 9/17/74 Carl Hobelman, Certificate of Service, Sept. 17, 1974 (Folder 388, Box 31)
  - 2338 9/18/74 HRFA Motion to Revise Hearing Schedule, Sept. 18, 1974 (Folder 389, Box 31)
  - 2338 9/27/74 Notice of Order of Witnesses, Sept. 27, 1974 (Folder 390, Box 31)
  - 2338 9/27/74 CE Response to HRFA Motion re Hearing Schedule, Sept. 27, 1974 (Folder 391, Box 31)
  - 2338 10/1/74 HRFA Motion Regarding Transcript, October 1, 1974 (Folder 392, Box 31)
  - 2338 10/1/74 Appeal from D. of Int. an order to stay Proceedings, October 1, 1974 (Folder 393, Box 31)
  - 2338 10/2/74 NYS Att.Gen Reply to Int. Depart. Appeal, October 2, 1974 (Folder 394, Box 31)
  - Staff Counsel’s answer to Dept. of Interior Appeal reschedule, October 4, 1974 (Folder 395, Box 31)
  - 2338 10/15/74 Interior on Scheduling, October 15, 1974 (Folder 396, Box 31)
  - Petition of Scenic Hudson to Reopen Licensing Proceedings in Full, October 21, 1974 (Folder 397, Box 31)
  - Order Directing Prompt Completion of Hearings, October 23, 1974 (Folder 398, Box 31)
  - Order Denying Appeals of Scenic Hudson, October 24, 1974 (Folder 399, Box 31)
  - Staff Opposition to Scenic Hudson Petition to Reopen Licensing Proceedings, Nov 7, 1974 (Folder 400, Box 31)
  - Con Ed Answer to Scenic Hudson Motion to Reopen Licensing Proceedings in Full, Nov 8, 1974 (Folder 401, Box 31)
  - Scenic Hudson Motion to Reopen Proceedings, Nov 16, 1974 (Folder 402, Box 31)
  - Scenic Hudson Reply to Con Ed and FPC Staff, Nov 16, 1974 (Folder 403, Box 31)
  - HRFA Response to Scenic Hudson Petition to Reopen, Nov 22, 1974 (Folder 404, Box 31)
  - Con Ed Answer to Scenic Hudson Motion to Reopen Proceeding, Nov 27, 1974 (Folder 405, Box 31)
  - HRFA Joins in Scenic Hudson’s Application for Rehearing, Dec 2, 1974 (Folder 406, Box 31)
  - Status Report and Responses, Nov, 1974 (Folder 407, Box 31)
  - Denial of Scenic Hudson’s Request for Reimbursement, Jan 15, 1975 (Folder 408, Box 31)
  - Report of Con Ed Response to FPC Order, Jan 30, 1975 (Folder 409, Box 31)
  - Reply of NYS Atty. Gen. To Scenic Hudson and HRFA Response to Con Ed Motions, Jan 8, 1975 (Folder 410, Box 31)
  - Order Denying Rehearing, Feb 21, 1975 (Folder 411, Box 31)
  - Answer of Scenic Hudson and HRFA to Con Ed Report and Motion re License, Sept 13, 1976 (Folder 412, Box 31)
  - FPC Staff Answer to Con Ed Report, Sept 15, 1976 (Folder 413, Box 31)
  - Motion to Reopen and Answer of Dept. Of Interior, Sept 15, 1976 (Folder 414, Box 31)
  - Answer of NYS Atty. Gen. And Motion to Terminate or Reopen, Sept 16, 1976 (Folder 415, Box 31)
  - Commission Staff Counsel Answer to Motions to Reopen, October 21, 1976 (Folder 416, Box 31)
  - Order Denying Motions to Terminate License and Reopen Record Without Prejudice, December 22, 1976 (Folder 417, Box 31)
  - Tenneco Atlantic Pipeline, January 6, 1977 (Folder 418, Box 31)
  - Order Granting Rehearing and Extension for Con Ed Fisheries Study, January 18, 1977 (Folder 419, Box 31)
  - Petition to Intervene, NYS Public Service Commission, January 24, 1977 (Folder 420, Box 31)
  - Order Dismissing Applications for Rehearing, February 11, 1977 (Folder 421, Box 31)
  - Order Clarifying Jurisdiction, March 16, 1977 (Folder 422, Box 31)
  - PSC Response in Support of Application for Rehearing, April 14, 1977 (Folder 423, Box 31)
  - Order Denying Application for Rehearing on Transmission Lines, April 20, 1977 (Folder 424, Box 31)
  - Testimony and Petitions (Folder 425, Box 32)
  - FPC 1966 Staff Testimony (Folder 426, Box 32)
  - FPC Testimony for Nov 14, 1966 Hearing, November 14, 1966 (Folder 427, Box 32)
  - Brooks Atkinson, FPC, 1969 (Folder 428, Box 33)
  - Babcock, Arnold - Testimony 11,12/ /66, December, 1966 (Folder 429, Box 33)
  - Deposition by Robert A. Baker, Vice President in charge of Electric Operations of Public Service Electric and Gas Co. (Folder 430, Box 33)
  - Richard P. Darden (Folder 431, Box 33)
  - William Bartlett (Folder 432, Box 33)
  - Milo C. Bell (Folder 433, Box 33)
  - Raymond E. Bell (Folder 434, Box 33)
  - Charles P. Benziger, FPC - 1969 (Con Ed.) (Folder 435, Box 33)
  - John A. Binner (Folder 436, Box 33)
  - William Blakey (Folder 437, Box 33)
  - David Brower (Folder 438, Box 33)
  - Robert S. Bryan (Folder 439, Box 33)
  - Thomas P. Callahan (Folder 440, Box 33)
  - Callison, FPC, 1966-1967 (Folder 441, Box 33)
  - Gordon K. Cameron (Folder 442, Box 33)
  - Town of Carmel (Putnam County) 10/11/66 (Folder 443, Box 33)
  - Citizens Committee for the Hudson Valley 11/14/66, November 14, 1966 (Folder 444, Box 33)
  - Citizens Committee on Natural Resources (Folder 445, Box 33)
  - Clark, John; Remarks (Folder 446, Box 33)
  - Gilmore D. Clarke (Folder 447, Box 33)
  - Deposition of W. J. Closs, March, 1967 (Folder 448, Box 33)
  - Rudolph J. Clauss (Folder 449, Box 33)
  - John V. Cleary (Folder 450, Box 33)
  - Commerce and Industry Association, September 2, 1966 (Folder 451, Box 33)
  - Conover, Herbert S. - Proposed Testimony and Prepared Testimony (Folder 452, Box 33)
  - FPC - 1966 - Con Ed. Testimony for Nov. 1966 Hearings, November, 1966 (Folder 453, Box 33)
  - Conservation League; 11/14/66, November 14, 1966 (Folder 454, Box 33)
  - Cook, Robert A. - Statement (Folder 455, Box 34)
  - J. Barry Cooke (Folder 456, Box 34)
  - Cornwall Taxpayers Water Protection Association (Folder 457, Box 34)
  - Cortlandt Conservation Association (Folder 458, Box 34)
  - F. N. Cuneo, 1969 (Folder 459, Box 34)
  - Ronald R. Dragon (Folder 460, Box 34)
  - H.P. Dain (Folder 461, Box 34)
  - H. W. Dierman (Folder 462, Box 34)
  - Joseph Dinunno (FPC Staff) (Folder 463, Box 34)
  - Donahue, Michael J. - Testimony 11,12/66, November 11, 1966 (Folder 464, Box 34)
  - Stephen Dorn (Folder 465, Box 34)
  - Jeremiah R. Downey (Folder 466, Box 34)
  - Rene Dubos (Folder 467, Box 34)
  - Testimony of T.C. Duncan, FPC - 1969 (Con Ed.) (Folder 468, Box 34)
  - Torris Eide (NYC) Direct Testimony 3/69, March, 1969 (Folder 469, Box 34)
  - Charles Eliot, FPC 1966 (Folder 470, Box 34)
  - Farnsworth, Margaret - Statement 11,12 /66, November 11, 1966 (Folder 471, Box 34)
  - Walter B. Fisk (Folder 472, Box 34)
  - Thomas W. Fluhr (NYC) Direct Testimony 3/69, March, 1969 (Folder 473, Box 34)
  - Portland P. Fox (Folder 474, Box 34)
  - Benjamin Frazier (Folder 475, Box 34)
  - Garrison Fish and Game (Folder 476, Box 34)
  - Garrison, Peter - Testimony (Folder 477, Box 34)
  - Gottschalk Testimony (Folder 478, Box 34)
  - Lorentz Graber - Mid Hudson Municipal Association (Folder 479, Box 34)
  - Rose Granovsky (Folder 480, Box 34)
  - Abraham Groopman (NYC) Direct Testimony, March, 1969 (Folder 481, Box 34)
  - Richard Edes Harrison (Folder 482, Box 34)
  - Forrest R. Hauck (Folder 483, Box 34)
  - Hempstead Town Lands Resources Council (Folder 484, Box 35)
  - Rev. William T. Hogan (Folder 485, Box 35)
  - Joseph Jessel (Folder 486, Box 35)
  - William N. Kinnard Jr. (Folder 487, Box 35)
  - Kusko, Alexander - Rebuttal Testimony (Folder 488, Box 35)
  - Mrs. Julia Lamb (Folder 489, Box 35)
  - Raymond A. Lester (Folder 490, Box 35)
  - George N. Lindsay (Folder 491, Box 35)
  - Ralph Longaker (Folder 492, Box 35)
  - McNew, Dr. George L. (Folder 493, Box 35)
  - Rebuttal Testimony - Hooper Pough (Folder 494, Box 35)
  - Rebuttal Testimony - Stannard Potter (Folder 495, Box 35)
  - Sachs, Reynolds M. - Rebuttal Testimony (Folder 496, Box 35)
  - Shepley, Jack M. - Rebuttal Testimony (Folder 497, Box 35)
  - Solters, Joseph J. Rebuttal Testimony (Folder 498, Box 35)
  - Waring, Mr. M. L. Prepared Rebuttal Testimony (Folder 499, Box 35)
  - FPC Exhibit # 280 - A; Mullarkey Exhibits # 1-15 (Folder 500, Box 36)
  - FPC Exhibit J - 1R -- J - 2R (Folder 501, Box 36)
  - FPC Exhibit K1 - K3 (Folder 502, Box 36)
  - FPC Exhibit S - 1R -- S - 13R and P1 (Folder 503, Box 36)
  - FPC Exhibits W1 - W6 (Folder 504, Box 36)
  - FPC Exhibit #’s 495 - 499 (Folder 505, Box 36)
  - FPC Exhibit #’s 500 - 507 (Folder 506, Box 36)
  - Listings of Intervenors (Folder 507, Box 36)
  - Proposed Transcript Corrections (For Various Files) FPC (Folder 508, Box 36)
  - Memo re: Proceedings 3/67, March, 1967 (Folder 509, Box 36)
  - Federal Powers Commission: Rules and Procedures, etc. (Folder 510, Box 36)
  - Notes on the Hearings, December 7, 1966 (Folder 511, Box 36)
  - FPC 1968-69; Certificate of Service (Con Ed.), 1968-1969 (Folder 512, Box 36)
  - Federal Power Commission: Power (Folder 513, Box 36)
  - Federal Power Commission: Storm King (Folder 514, Box 36)
  - Federal Power Commission: Ichthyoplankton River Survey Prog., Texas Inst., Inc., 1973-75, 1973-1975 (Folder 515, Box 37)
  - Federal Power Commission: Fishery Studies, 1974-75, 1974-1975 (Folder 516, Box 37)
  - Federal Power Commission: Fishery Studies, 1974-1975 (Folder 517, Box 37)
  - Federal Power Commission: Fishery Study for Con Ed. By UMA Engineering Pacific, Inc., December 15, 1974 (Folder 518, Box 37)
  - Federal Power Commission: October Fisherings, July - October 14, 1974 (Folder 519, Box 37)
  - Federal Power Commission: October Fisherings, October 15, 1974 - March 1975 (Folder 520, Box 37)
  - Federal Power Commission: Corres, re. Fisheries Studies, 1973-1974 (Folder 521, Box 37)
  - FPC - Joseph C. Swindler speech before Edison Electric Inst., June 4, 1963 (Folder 522, Box 38)
  - FPC Statement of Edward C. Crafts 10/12/66; Director of Bureau of Outdoor Recreation, October 12, 1966 (Folder 523, Box 38)
  - Federal Power Commission: Lee C. White - Statements and Addresses, May - December, 1966 (Folder 524, Box 38)
  - Federal Power Commission: Remarks of Comm. John A. Carver, Jr., San Francisco, December 1, 1969 (Folder 525, Box 38)
  - Nassikas Remarks at Electrical World Conference, January 14, 1971 (Folder 526, Box 38)
  - Federal Power Commission: Memo re: Reports to FPC, May, 1971 (Folder 527, Box 38)
  - Federal Power Commission: Planning Status Reports (Folder 528, Box 38)
  - FPC Annual Report, 1966 (Folder 529, Box 38)
  - FPC Annual Report, 1969 (Folder 530, Box 38)
  - Federal Power Commission: Correspondence, 1964-1967, and undated (Folder 531, Box 38)
  - Federal Power Commission: Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Folder 532, Box 38)
  - Federal Power Commission: Clippings, 1968-1969 (Folder 533, Box 38)
  - Federal Power Commission: Releases, 1964-1965 (Folder 534, Box 39)
  - Federal Power Commission: Releases, 1968-1971 (Folder 535, Box 39)
  - Federal Power Commission: News Digest, 1964-1966 (Folder 536, Box 39)
  - Federal Power Commission: FPC News, January - April 1973 (Folder 537, Box 39)
  - Federal Power Commission: FPC News, May - June, 1973 (Folder 538, Box 39)
  - Federal Power Commission: FPC News, July - Aug. 1973, July - August, 1973 (Folder 539, Box 39)
  - Federal Power Commission: FPC News, September - December, 1973 (Folder 540, Box 39)
  - Supreme Court of the United States Oct. Term, 1971; Scenic Hudson Preservation Conference… v. Federal Power Commission and Con Ed. (Folder 541, Box 40)
  - An Informal Explanation of the Organization and Work of the Federal Power Commission (Folder 542, Box 40)
  - United States of America Federal Power Commission; Regulations under the Federal Power Act, In Effect Jan. 1, 1970, January 1, 1970 (Folder 543, Box 40)
  - Transmittal Sheet No. 3 to Regulations Under the Federal Power Act, September 16, 1966 (Folder 544, Box 40)
  - The 1970 National Power Survey; Federal Powers Commission Part II (Folder 545, Box 40)
  - United States of America Before the Federal Power Commission - In the Matter of Con. Ed. Co. of NY, Inc.; Brief on Exceptions of Sierra Club and its Atlantic Chapter to Initial Decision of Examiner (Folder 546, Box 40)
  - United States of America Federal Power Commission, Washington D.C.: In the Matter of the Consolidated Edison Co. of New York Inc.; Brief on Behalf of Scenic Hudson Preservation Conference, Intervenor, Volume I Points I-V (Folder 547, Box 40)
  - Statistics of Privately Owned Electric Utilities in the United States, 1968 (Folder 548, Box 40)
  - Statistics of Publicly Owned Electric Utilities in the United States, 1967 (Folder 549, Box 40)
  - United States of America Federal Power Commission; Opinion No. 584, Consolidated Edison Company of New York Inc.; Opinion and Order Issuing License Under Part I of the Federal Power Act (Folder 550, Box 40)
  - United States of America Before the Federal Power Commission, In the Matter of Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc.; Brief of Applicant Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc., After Further Hearings on Remand (Folder 551, Box 40)
- 5. Fund Raising and Related Materials, 1965-1974; 5; About 2 linear feet Boxes: 41 - 46 Folders: 552 - 680
  Series contains information on fund raising activities, including mailings, hikes, boat rides, cocktail parties, etc.; correspondence regarding the exchange of mailing lists with other organizations; general background information; and newsletter materials.
  - Special Fund-Raising Letters (Possible Large Contributors) (Folder 552, Box 41)
  - Scenic Hudson Printed Material (Folder 553, Box 41)
  - Princeton Luncheon, 5/26/66 (Folder 554, Box 41)
  - Harvard Club Cocktail Party 11/10/66 (Folder 555, Box 41)
  - Special Letters of Interest from S. Hudson Contributors (Folder 556, Box 41)
  - Boat Trip - Circle Line, Nov. 18, 1967; Clips (Folder 557, Box 41)
  - Fund Raising Letters of Appeal - Special (Folder 558, Box 41)
  - Suppliers, Letters (Folder 559, Box 41)
  - Draft: Boat Ride Brochure 2/19/68; “1967 On the River” (Folder 560, Box 41)
  - Information on L.O. Rothschild (used at Rothschild Recpt. 6/26/68) (Folder 561, Box 41)
  - Fund Raising Circle Line and Literature, Nov. 18, 1967 (Folder 562, Box 41)
  - Rothschild, L.O. Reception, 6/26/68 (Folder 563, Box 41)
  - Rothschild, L.O., See: 1.Scenic Hudson Preservation Conf.; 2.Union Electric’s Pumped Storage Plant (Folder 564, Box 41)
  - May 20, 1969; Citizen Cons. Conference, Position Statement (Folder 565, Box 41)
  - Salute to Storm King 8/26/69 (Folder 566, Box 41)
  - Fund Raising, 1969-70 (Folder 567, Box 41)
  - May 13, 1970; Event. Yacht Club (Folder 568, Box 41)
  - Boats - Charter (Sea Club) (Folder 569, Box 41)
  - Statements for Boat Ride Brochure (Folder 570, Box 41)
  - Event (Circle Line) Oct. 3, 1970 (Folder 571, Box 41)
  - Mailing Lists 1963-64 (Folder 572, Box 42)
  - Mailing Lists Background Material, 1964 (Folder 573, Box 42)
  - Mailing Lists 1965 (Folder 574, Box 42)
  - Mailing Lists 1965 (Folder 575, Box 42)
  - Mailing to Kiwanis Club, Granges etc. (1966) (Folder 576, Box 42)
  - Mailing Lists 1966 (Folder 577, Box 42)
  - Newspaper Lists (Folder 578, Box 42)
  - Mailing Lists 1966-74 (Folder 579, Box 43)
  - Mailing Lists - Undated (Folder 580, Box 43)
  - Mailing Lists - Undated (Folder 581, Box 43)
  - Macres, Thomas - Environment II, 1971 (Folder 582, Box 43)
  - Thomas Macres (Folder 583, Box 43)
  - Albert Schweitzer Hospital (584, Box 44)
  - American Association for Indian Affairs; Sylvia Hermelin (Folder 585, Box 44)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (Folder 586, Box 44)
  - Ben Peterson (Amer. Comm. On Africa Nat’l Sharecroppers Fund) (SEDF) (Folder 587, Box 44)
  - The American Forestry Association (Folder 588, Box 44)